<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ANKO layout</string>
    <string name="LongText">the country\'s primary competitio). At the to
        p of the Australian league system, it is the country\'s primary competiti
        o, it is the country\'s primary competition fothe country\'s primary competitio). A
        t the top of the Australian league system, it is the country\'s primary competitio,
        it is the country\'s primary competition fothe country\'s primary competitio). At the top of the Australi
        an league system, it is the country\'s primary competitio, it is the country\'s primary competition fo the c
        ountry\'s primary competitio). At the top of the Australian league system, it is the country\'s primary compe
        titio, it is the country\'s primary the country\'s primary competitio). At the top of the Australian league system,
        it is the country\'s primary competitio, it is the country\'s primary competition fothe country\'s primary competi
        tio). At the top of the Australian league system, it is the country\'s primary competitio, it is the country\'s prima
        ry competition fothe country\'s primary competitio). At the top of the Australian league system, it is the country\'
        s primary competitio, it is the country\'s primary competition fothe country\'s primary competitio). At the top of th
        e Australian league system, it is the country\'s primary competitio, it is the country\'s primary competition fothe c
        ountry\'s primary competitio). At the top of the Australian league system, it is the country\'s primary competitio, it
        is the country\'s primary competition fothe country\'s primary competitio). At the top of the Australian league sys
        tem, it is the country\'s primary competitio, it is the country\'s primary competition fothe country\'s primary com
        petitio). At the top of the Australian league system, it is the country\'s primary competitio, it is the country\'s
        primary competition fothe country\'s primary competitio). At the top of the Australian league system, it is the co
        untry\'s primary competitio, it is the country\'s primary competition fothe country\'s primary competitio). At the
        top of the Australian league system, it is the country\'s primary competitio, it is the country\'s primary compet
        ition fothe country\'s primary competitio). At the top of the Australian league system, it is the country\'s prim
        ary competitio, it is the country\'s primary competition focompetition for the sport. The A-League was establis
        hed in 2004 as a successor to the National Soccer League (NSL) and competition commenced in August 2005. The le
        ague is currently contested by ten teams; nine based in Australia and one based in New Zealand. It is known as the Hyundai A-League (HAL) through a sponsorship arrangement with the Hyundai Motor Company.</string>
</resources>
